A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 100 International - Series 253 Washington FA387a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United States, 1929-1977; 200; 113 box(es)
  - Educational Services, Inc. - Summer Institutes, September 1964-1967 (Box 32, Folder 263)
  - Educational Services, Inc. - Summer Institutes, September 1964-1967 (Box 32, Folder 264)
  - Educational Services, Inc. - Summer Institutes, September 1964-1967 (Box 32, Folder 265)
  - Educational Services, Inc. - Summer Institutes - Supplemental Material, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 266)
  - Educational Services, Inc. - Summer Institutes - Supplemental Material, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 267)
  - Evanston - Education - Integration Evaluation, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 268)
  - Evanston - Education - Integration Evaluation, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 269)
  - Evanston - Education - Integration Evaluation, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 270)
  - Evanston - Education - Integration Evaluation, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 271)
  - Evanston - Education - Integration Evaluation, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 272)
  - Evanston - Education - Integration Evaluation - Supplementary Material, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 273)
  - Evanston - Education - Integration Evaluation - Supplementary Material, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 274)
  - Experiment in International Living - New York Ambassadors - (Foreign Exchange Program), 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 275)
  - Federal Council of the Churches - (Church and Economic Life), 1947- October 1948 (Box 33, Folder 276)
  - Federal Council of the Churches - (Church and Economic Life), 1947- October 1948 (Box 33, Folder 277)
  - Federal Council of the Churches - (Church and Economic Life), November 1948-1965 (Box 34, Folder 278)
  - Federal Council of the Churches - (Church and Economic Life), November 1948-1965 (Box 34, Folder 279)
  - Federal Council of the Churches - (Church and Economic Life), November 1948-1965 (Box 34, Folder 280)
  - Federal Council of the Churches - (Church and Economic Life), November 1948-1965 (Box 34, Folder 281)
  - Federal Council of the Churches - (Church and Economic Life), November 1948-1965 (Box 34, Folder 282)
  - Federal Council of the Churches - (Church and Economic Life), November 1948-1965 (Box 34, Folder 283)
  - Federal Council of the Churches - (Church and Economic Life), November 1948-1965 (Box 34, Folder 284)
  - Fisk University - Development Program - Faculty Housing, 1966-1970 (Box 35, Folder 285)
  - Fisk University - Development Program - Library, 1965-1968 (Box 35, Folder 286)
  - Fisk University - Development Program - Planning Retreats, 1969-1973 (Box 35, Folder 287)
  - Fisk University - Development Program - Surveys, 1965-1970 (Box 35, Folder 288)
  - Fisk University - Development Program - Surveys - Supplemental Material, 1964-1968 (Box 35, Folder 289)
  - Fisk University - Development Program - Surveys - Supplemental Material, 1964-1968 (Box 35, Folder 290)
  - Fisk University - Development Program - Surveys - Supplemental Material, 1964-1968 (Box 35, Folder 291)
  - Fisk University - Development Program - Surveys - Supplemental Material, 1964-1968 (Box 35, Folder 292)
  - Fisk University - Pre-College Center, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 293)
  - Ford Foundation - Educational Television Conference, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 294)
  - Ford Foundation - Latin American Program - Conference, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 295)
  - Ford Foundation - Latin American Program - Conferences - Printed Material, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 296)
  - Foundation Executives Conference, 1966-1969 (Box 36, Folder 297)
  - Foundation Executives Conference, 1966-1969 (Box 36, Folder 298)
  - Foundation Library Center, 1960-1962 (Box 36, Folder 299)
  - Foundations, Criticism of, 1913-1941 (Box 36, Folder 300)
  - Foundations, Criticism of, 1913-1941 (Box 36, Folder 301)
  - Foundations, Criticism of, 1942-1969 (Box 37, Folder 302)
  - Foundations, Criticism of, 1942-1969 (Box 37, Folder 303)
  - Foundations, Criticism of, 1942-1969 (Box 37, Folder 304)
  - Foundations, Criticism of, 1942-1969 (Box 37, Folder 305)
  - Foundations, Criticism of, 1942-1969 (Box 37, Folder 306)
  - Foundations, Criticism of, 1942-1969 (Box 37, Folder 307)
  - Foundations, Criticism of - Newspaper Articles, 1916-1927 (Box 37, Folder 308)
  - Foundations, Criticism of - American Legion, 1954-1956 (Box 38, Folder 309)
  - Foundations, Criticism of - American Legion, 1954-1956 (Box 38, Folder 310)
  - Foundations, Criticism of - B - L (Box 38, Folder 311)
  - Foundations, Criticism of - B - L (Box 38, Folder 312)
  - Foundations, Criticism of - M - Ramsey (Box 38, Folder 313)
  - Foundations, Criticism of - Riley (Box 38, Folder 314)
  - Foundations, Criticism of - Rose - W (Box 38, Folder 315)
  - Freedom House - University Unrest - (Conference), 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 316)
  - Freedom House - University Unrest - Supplemental Material, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 317)
  - Friends Neighborhood Guild - (Counseling Program), 1965-1970, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 318)
  - Friends Neighborhood Guild - (Counseling Program), 1965-1970, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 319)
  - Friends Neighborhood Guild - (Counseling Program), 1965-1970, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 320)
  - Friends Neighborhood Guild - (Counseling Program), 1965-1970, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 321)
  - Friends Neighborhood Guild - (Counseling Program), 1965-1970, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 322)
  - Friends Neighborhood Guild - (Counseling Program), 1965-1970, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 323)
  - Friends Neighborhood Guild - (Counseling Program), 1965-1970, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 324)
  - Friends Neighborhood Guild - Supplemental Material, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 325)
  - Friends Neighborhood Guild - Supplemental Material, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 326)
  - Fry, Alderson F. - (Library Consultant, Travel Grant), 1963-1965 (Box 40, Folder 327)
  - Gary - Education, 1968-1972 (Box 40, Folder 328)
  - Gary - Education, 1968-1972 (Box 40, Folder 329)
  - Gary - Education, 1968-1972 (Box 40, Folder 330)
  - Gary - Education, 1968-1972 (Box 40, Folder 331)
  - Gary - Education, 1968-1972 (Box 40, Folder 332)
  - Gary - Education, 1968-1972 (Box 40, Folder 333)
  - Gary - Education, 1968-1972 (Box 40, Folder 334)
  - Gary - Education - Supplemental Material, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 335)
  - Gary - Education - Supplemental Material, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 336)
  - Gary - Education - Leadership Training, 1969-1972 (Box 41, Folder 337)
  - Germanistic Society of America - Publications, 1947-1949 (Box 41, Folder 338)
  - Germanistic Society of America - Publications, 1947-1949 (Box 41, Folder 339)
  - Germanistic Society of America - Publications, 1947-1949 (Box 41, Folder 340)
  - Germanistic Society of America - Publications, 1947-1949 (Box 41, Folder 341)
  - Germanistic Society of America - Publications, 1947-1949 (Box 41, Folder 342)
  - Germanistic Society of America - Publications, 1950-1956 (Box 42, Folder 343)
  - Germanistic Society of America - Publications, 1950-1956 (Box 42, Folder 344)
  - Germanistic Society of America - Publications, 1950-1956 (Box 42, Folder 345)
  - Germanistic Society of America - Publications, 1950-1956 (Box 42, Folder 346)
  - Greater Cleveland Associated Foundation, 1967-1972 (Box 42, Folder 347)
  - Greater Cleveland Associated Foundation - Supplemental Material, 1966-1967, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 348)
  - Greater Cleveland Associated Foundation - Supplemental Material, 1966-1967, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 349)
  - Greenhall, Arthur - (Travel Grant), 1956-1957 (Box 43, Folder 350)
  - Gulf Coast Research Laboratory, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 351)
  - Hampton Institute - (Academic Reinforcement for Entering Students), 1963-1964, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 352)
  - Hampton Institute - (Academic Reinforcement for Entering Students), 1963-1964, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 353)
  - Hampton Institute - (Academic Reinforcement for Entering Students), 1963-1964, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 354)
  - Hampton Institute - (Academic Reinforcement for Entering Students) - Supplemental Material (Box 43, Folder 355)
  - Hampton Institute - (Academic Reinforcement for Entering Students) - Supplemental Material (Box 43, Folder 356)
  - Harlem Commonwealth Council, Inc. - Loan Service, 1969-1971 (Box 43, Folder 357)
  - Harlem Commonwealth Council, Inc. - Loan Service - Supplemental Material, 1968; 1 item (Box 43, Folder 358)
  - Harlem Commonwealth Council, Inc. - Loan Service - Supplemental Material, 1968; 2 items (Box 44, Folder 359)
  - Harvard University - Bender, Wilbur J. - (Travel Grant), 1954-1956 (Box 44, Folder 360)
  - Harvard University - Collective Negotiations Institute - (School of Education), 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 361)
  - Harvard University - Collective Negotiations Institute - (School of Education), 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 362)
  - Harvard University - Creative Thinking - (Bruner, Jerome), 1959-1961 (Box 44, Folder 363)
  - Harvard University - Curriculum Revision - (School of Public Health), 1962-1963, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 364)
  - Harvard University - Development Advisory Conference, 1965-1966 (Box 44, Folder 365)
  - Harvard University - Educational Leadership, 1968-1972 (Box 44, Folder 366)
  - Harvard University - Educational Leadership, 1968-1972 (Box 44, Folder 367)
  - Harvard University - Educational Leadership, 1968-1972 (Box 44, Folder 368)
  - Harvard University - Indian Population - (Gordon, John E.), 1953-1961 (Box 45, Folder 369)
  - Harvard University - Indian Population - (Gordon, John E.), 1953-1961 (Box 45, Folder 370)
  - Harvard University - Indian Population - (Gordon, John E.), 1953-1961 (Box 45, Folder 371)
  - Harvard University - Indian Population - (Gordon, John E.), 1953-1961 (Box 45, Folder 372)
  - Harvard University - Indian Population - (Gordon, John E.) - Supplemental Material, 1953-1955 (Box 45, Folder 373)
  - Harvard University - Indian Population - (Gordon, John E.) - Supplemental Material, 1953-1955 (Box 45, Folder 374)
  - Harvard University - Indian Population - (Gordon, John E.) - Supplemental Material, 1955-1956 (Box 46, Folder 375)
  - Harvard University - Indian Population - (Gordon, John E.) - Supplemental Material, 1955-1956 (Box 46, Folder 376)
  - Harvard University - Indian Population - Wyon, John B., 1957-1959 (Box 46, Folder 377)
  - Harvard University - International Student Center - (School of Public Health), 1960-1962 (Box 46, Folder 378)
  - Harvard University - Law School - Negro Students, 1964-1968, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 379)
  - Harvard University - Law School - Negro Students, 1964-1968, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 380)
  - Harvard University - Michelson, Edward H. - (Travel Grant), 1964-1966 (Box 46, Folder 381)
  - Harvard University - Newton's Principia - (Cohen, I. Bernard and Foley, Margaret G.), 1956-1969 (Box 46, Folder 382)
  - Harvard University - Nutrition - (Stare, Frederick), 1960-1963 (Box 46, Folder 383)
  - Harvard University - Nutrition - (Stare, Frederick), 1960-1963 (Box 46, Folder 384)
  - Harvard University - Radiation, 1957-1972 (Box 47, Folder 385)
  - Harvard University - Radiation, 1957-1972 (Box 47, Folder 386)
  - Harvard University - Russian Exchange, 1958-1960, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 387)
  - Harvard University - Visits, 1960-1961 (Box 47, Folder 388)
  - Harvard University - Weller, Thomas H. - (Travel Grant), 1969 (Box 47, Folder 389)
  - Haverford College - African Civilization, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 390)
  - Haverford College - Negro Administration - (Robinson, Bruce N.), 1968-1972 (Box 47, Folder 391)
  - Health Agencies - Appraisal, 1958-June 1961 (Box 47, Folder 392)
  - Health Agencies - Appraisal, 1958-June 1961 (Box 47, Folder 393)
  - Health Agencies - Appraisal, 1958-June 1961 (Box 47, Folder 394)
  - Health Agencies - Appraisal, 1958-June 1961 (Box 47, Folder 395)
  - Health Agencies - Appraisal, July 1961-1967 (Box 48, Folder 396)
  - Health Agencies - Appraisal, July 1961-1967 (Box 48, Folder 397)
  - Health Agencies - Appraisal - Supplemental Material, 1957-1958, 1960-1961 (Box 48, Folder 398)
  - Health Agencies - Appraisal - Supplemental Material, 1957-1958, 1960-1961 (Box 48, Folder 399)
  - Health Agencies - Appraisal - Supplemental Material, 1957-1958, 1960-1961 (Box 48, Folder 400)
  - Health Agencies - Appraisal - Supplemental Material, 1957-1958, 1960-1961 (Box 48, Folder 401)
  - Health Agencies - Appraisal - Supplemental Material, 1957-1958, 1960-1961 (Box 48, Folder 402)
  - Health Agencies - Appraisal - Supplemental Material, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 403)
  - Health Insurance Plan, 1953-1958 (Box 49, Folder 404)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material, 1945-1948 (Box 49, Folder 405)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material, 1945-1948 (Box 49, Folder 406)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material, 1945-1948 (Box 49, Folder 407)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material, 1945-1948 (Box 49, Folder 408)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material, 1949-1955 (Box 50, Folder 409)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material, 1949-1955 (Box 50, Folder 410)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material, 1949-1955 (Box 50, Folder 411)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material - (Household Survey), 1952 (Box 50, Folder 412)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material - (Household Survey), 1952 (Box 50, Folder 413)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material - (Newsletter), 1947-1951 (Box 50, Folder 414)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material - (Newsletter), 1947-1951 (Box 50, Folder 415)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material - Steering Committee Meeting, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 416)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material - Steering Committee Meeting, 1952-1953 (Box 51, Folder 417)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Supplemental Material - Steering Committee Meeting, 1952-1953 (Box 51, Folder 418)
  - Health Insurance Plan - Hypertension, 1957-1959 (Box 51, Folder 419)
  - Herald Tribune Fresh Air Fund - Russian Film, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 420)
  - Hospitality and Information Service - (Diplomat Recreation), 1961-1965 (Box 51, Folder 421)
  - Hospitality and Information Service - Supplemental Material, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 422)
  - Hotchkiss School - Remedial Education, 1963-1967 (Box 51, Folder 423)
  - Hotchkiss School - Remedial Education, 1963-1967 (Box 51, Folder 424)
  - Hotchkiss School - Remedial Education, 1963-1967 (Box 51, Folder 425)
  - Hotchkiss School - Remedial Education, 1963-1967 (Box 51, Folder 426)
  - Hotchkiss School - Remedial Education, 1968-1970 (Box 52, Folder 427)
  - Hotchkiss School - Remedial Education, 1968-1970 (Box 52, Folder 428)
  - Human Relations Task Force - Youth Placement Corps, 1969-1970 (Box 52, Folder 429)
  - Hunter College - Faculty Research Fund, 1956-1960 (Box 52, Folder 430)
  - Hunter College - Governance Plan, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 431)
  - Hunter College High School - Remedial Education, 1965-1968 (Box 52, Folder 432)
  - Independent Schools Foundation of Massachusetts, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 52, Folder 433)
  - Independent Schools Talent Search Program (Boston) - (Summer Program), 1966-1969 (Box 52, Folder 434)
  - Independent Schools Talent Search Program (Boston) - (Summer Program), 1966-1969 (Box 52, Folder 435)
  - Independent Schools Talent Search Program (Boston) - (Summer Program), 1970-1972 (Box 53, Folder 436)
  - Independent Schools Talent Search Program (Boston) - (Summer Program), 1970-1972 (Box 53, Folder 437)
  - Independent Schools Talent Search Program (Boston) - Supplemental Material, 1968-1982; 5 items (Box 53, Folder 438)
  - Insect Pests - Conference, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 439)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs - Middle North Survey, 1966-1968 (Box 53, Folder 440)
  - Institute of International Education, 1947-1948 (Box 53, Folder 441)
  - Institute of International Education, 1947-1948 (Box 53, Folder 442)
  - Institute of International Education, 1949-March 1955 (Box 54, Folder 443)
  - Institute of International Education, 1949-March 1955 (Box 54, Folder 444)
  - Institute of International Education, 1949-March 1955 (Box 54, Folder 445)
  - Institute of International Education, 1949-March 1955 (Box 54, Folder 446)
  - Institute of International Education, 1949-March 1955 (Box 54, Folder 447)
  - Institute of International Education, 1949-March 1955 (Box 54, Folder 448)
  - Institute of International Education, 1949-March 1955 (Box 54, Folder 449)
  - Institute of International Education, 1949-March 1955 (Box 54, Folder 450)
  - Institute of International Education, April 1955-1956 (Box 55, Folder 451)
  - Institute of International Education, April 1955-1956 (Box 55, Folder 452)
  - Institute of International Education - Colombian Student Roster, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 453)
  - Institute of International Education - Hungarian Students, 1956-1958 (Box 55, Folder 454)
  - Institute of International Education - Inter-American Exchange of Persons, 1958-1959 (Box 55, Folder 455)
  - Institute of International Education - Russian Briefing Service, 1960-1965 (Box 55, Folder 456)
  - Institute of International Education - Russian Seminars, 1959-1963 (Box 55, Folder 457)
  - Institute of International Education - Russian Seminars, 1959-1963 (Box 55, Folder 458)
  - Institute of Judicial Administration, Inc., 1952-1959 (Box 56, Folder 459)
  - Institute of Judicial Administration, Inc., 1952-1959 (Box 56, Folder 460)
  - Institute of Judicial Administration, Inc., 1952-1959 (Box 56, Folder 461)
  - Institute of Judicial Administration, Inc. - Report of Activities, 1952-1956 (Box 56, Folder 462)
  - Institute of Judicial Administration, Inc. - Conference, 1955-November 1956 (Box 56, Folder 463)
  - Institute in Religion in an Age of Science - Conference, December 1956-1962 (Box 57, Folder 464)
  - Institute in Religion in an Age of Science - Conference, December 1956-1962 (Box 57, Folder 465)
  - Institute in Religion in an Age of Science - Conference, December 1956-1962 (Box 57, Folder 466)
  - Institute of Society, Ethics and the Life Sciences - (No Grant Made), 1971 (Box 57, Folder 467)
  - Institute for the Study of Health and Society, 1970-1974 (Box 57, Folder 468)
  - International House - Alumni Conference, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 469)
  - Inter-University Case Program, 1961-1962 (Box 57, Folder 470)
  - Inter-University Case Program, 1961-1962 (Box 57, Folder 471)
  - Iowa State University - Automotive Scrap Recycling, 1970-1972 (Box 58, Folder 472)
  - Jessup, Philip C. - (Travel Grant), 1962-1963 (Box 58, Folder 473)
  - Jesuit Educational Association - Rooney, Edward B. - (Travel Grant), 1957-1963 (Box 58, Folder 474)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Patterson, Athol J. - (International Health Association), 1958-1960, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 475)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Radiation, 1957-1960, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 476)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Radiation, 1957-1960, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 477)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Rodent Ecology, 1944-1952 (Box 58, Folder 478)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Rodent Ecology, 1944-1952 (Box 58, Folder 479)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Rodent Ecology - Reports, 1945-1949, n.d.; 16 items contained in folders 480-481. (Box 59, Folder 480)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Rodent Ecology - Reports, 1945-1949, n.d.; 16 items contained in folders 480-481. (Box 59, Folder 481)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Spillett, J. Juan - (Bandicoot Rat Study), 1968-1971 (Box 59, Folder 482)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Spillett, J. Juan - "The Ecology of the Lesser Bandicoot Rat in Calcutta", 1968 (Box 59, Folder 483)
  - Johnson, Jacob B. - (Public Administration), 1968, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 484)
  - Journal of Medical Education - Foreigns Subscriptions, 1957-1962 (Box 59, Folder 485)
  - Library of Congress - Mumford, L. Quincy - (Travel Grant, Nutrition), 1963-1966 (Box 59, Folder 486)
  - Lincoln University - Milner, Ronald - (Writer in Residence), 1965-1969 (Box 59, Folder 487)
  - Lincoln University - Remedial Education, 1963-1964 (Box 59, Folder 488)
  - Lincoln University - Remedial Education, 1963-1966 (Box 59, Folder 489)
  - Lincoln University - Remedial Education, 1963-1966 (Box 59, Folder 490)
  - Lincoln University - Remedial Education - Supplemental Material (Box 60, Folder 491)
  - Lincoln University - Student Assistance, 1965-1973 (Box 60, Folder 492)
  - Longnecker, Herbert E. - (Travel Grant, Education), 1960 (Box 60, Folder 493)
  - Macy Foundation - Family Planning Conference, 1966-1970 (Box 60, Folder 494)
  - Macy Foundation - Midwives Conference, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 495)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Clean Air Car Race, 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 496)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Clean Air Car Race, 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 497)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Environmental Changes, 1969-June 1970 (Box 60, Folder 498)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Environmental Changes, 1969-June 1970 (Box 60, Folder 499)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Environmental Changes, July 1970-1971; 1234698 (Box 61, Folder 500)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Environmental Changes, July 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 501)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Environmental Changes, July 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 502)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Psychology, 1962 - 1963 (Box 61, Folder 503)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Russian Science, 1956-1957 (Box 61, Folder 504)
  - Maxwell, W. H. - (Relief, New York City), 1915 (Box 61, Folder 505)
  - McCandless, David A. - (Travel Grant, Police Education), 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 506)
  - Medical Library Center of New York, 1959-1964 (Box 61, Folder 507)
  - Medical Library Center of New York, 1959-1964 (Box 61, Folder 508)
  - Medical Library Center of New York - Reports, 1959-1961; 3 items (Box 61, Folder 509)
  - Memorial Hospital - Khanolkar, V. R. - (Visiting Researcher), 1962-1963 (Box 61, Folder 510)
  - Miami University - Nielson, Read R. - (Visiting Professor, Zoology), 1968-1971 (Box 61, Folder 511)
  - Michigan State University - Admissions, 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 512)
  - Michigan State University - Hannah, John A. - (Travel Grant), 1965 (Box 62, Folder 513)
  - Miles College - Shaw, Francis H. - (Visiting Professor, History), 1964-1965 (Box 62, Folder 514)
  - Mills College - International Student Program - Rotunda, Dominic P., 1956-1957 (Box 62, Folder 515)
  - Monroe County Community College - Environmental Quality, 1969-1973 (Box 62, Folder 516)
  - Monroe County Community College - Environmental Quality, 1969-1973 (Box 62, Folder 517)
  - Morehouse College - Intensive Study Program, 1963-1969 (Box 62, Folder 518)
  - Morehouse College - Intensive Study Program, 1963-1969 (Box 62, Folder 519)
  - Morehouse College - Intensive Study Program, 1963-1969 (Box 62, Folder 520)
  - Morehouse College - Intensive Study Program - Report, 1965; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 521)
  - Morehouse College - Intensive Study Program - Report, 1965; 1 item (Box 63, Folder 522)
  - Morehouse College - Mays, Benjamin E. - (Grant in Aid, Autobiography), 1967-1972 (Box 63, Folder 523)
  - Morehouse College - Mays, Benjamin E. - (Grant in Aid, Autobiography), 1967-1972 (Box 63, Folder 524)
  - Morton Memorial Foundation - (Conference Center), 1965-1966 (Box 63, Folder 525)
  - Mount Holyoke College - Ludington, Flora B. - (Travel Grant, Library Science), 1958-1959 (Box 63, Folder 526)
  - Mount Holyoke College - Remedial Education, 1964-1970 (Box 63, Folder 527)
  - Mount Holyoke College - Remedial Education, 1964-1970 (Box 63, Folder 528)
  - Mount Holyoke College - Remedial Education - Reports, 1965-1967, 1968; 4 items contained in folders 529-530. (Box 63, Folder 529)
  - Mount Holyoke College - Remedial Education - Reports, 1965-1967, 1968; 4 items contained in folders 529-530. (Box 63, Folder 530)
  - Mutants of Maize - (Report Publication), 1967-1970 (Box 64, Folder 531)